Isis Kitcher

JUNIOR FULL STACK
DEVELOPER

Details

London, United Kingdom 07429629092 <u>kitcher96@gmail.com</u>

Links

Resume Website

<u>Github</u>

<u>LinkedIn</u>

Technical Skills

Languages:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Python

Frameworks:

- Bootstrap
- Django
- Flask
- jQuery

Version Control:

- Git
- GitHub

Databases:

- PostgreSQL
- MongoDB

API:

Stripe

Host:

- Heroku
- Cloudinary

Professional Summary

As a motivated and adaptable graduate, I have acquired a diverse set of skills in both front-end and back-end development over the past three years. My focus has been on obtaining certification in full stack development from Code Institute, while juggling work and studies. I have a particular interest in Bootstrap and Django frameworks and continuously strive to expand my knowledge of other beneficial frameworks.

With a passion for web development and a strong work ethic, I am excited to take the next step in my career by joining a team as a junior web developer. I am eager to further develop my skills and gain hands-on experience in the field while contributing to projects and growing with the company.

Education

Code Institute - Diploma in Full Stack Development

SEPTEMBER 2021 — DECEMBER 2022

Graduated a universally renowned Full stack e-commerce boot camp.

Kingston University - Software Engineering

SEPTEMBER 2014 — SEPTEMBER 2016

Completed 2/3 years.

Christ The King Sixth Form College - A level

SEPTEMBER 2012 — SEPTEMBER 2014

Achieved A Levels in Computer Science, Business Studies and History.

St. Thomas the Apostle College - GCSE

SEPTEMBER 2007 — SEPTEMBER 2012

8 GCSE grades including English, Science and Maths.

Projects

Myrag - Django Framework

E-commerce site for a variety of head wraps

https://myrag.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/myrag

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Python3, Django, PostgreSQL, Cloudinary, Heroku, Stripe.

Sandra's Kitchen - Django Framework

Booking app for a restaurant

https://sandras-kitchen.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/sandras-kitchen

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla JS, JQuery, Bootstrap, Git, GitHub, Python3, Django, PostgreSQL, Cloudinary, Heroku.

Battleships - Python

Strategy game that replicates the classic Battleships game

https://devisis-battleships.herokuapp.com/

https://github.com/devisis/battleships

Technologies Used: Python3, Git, GitHub, Heroku.

It's Coming Home

Website documenting England's progress in EURO 2020

https://devisis.github.io/its-coming-home/england.html

https://github.com/devisis/its-coming-home

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Git, GitHub.

Rock Paper Scissors Lizard Spock - Vanilla JS

RNG game of rock paper scissors

https://devisis.github.io/rock-paper-scissors-lizard-spock/

https://github.com/devisis/rock-paper-scissors-lizard-spock

Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, Vanilla Js, Git, GitHub.

Work Experience

Thames Clippers

Deckhand

FEBRUARY 2019 —PRESENT

- Maintain up-to-date documentation throughout the day, ensuring accuracy and completeness.
- Assess safety issues on board the vessel, identifying and addressing potential risks in a timely and effective manner.
- Conduct safety training sessions, effectively communicating safety protocols and procedures.

Barista

June 2018 — February 2019

- Apply attention to detail in adhering to health and safety regulations to ensure a safe environment for customers.
- Complete documentation accurately and efficiently, developing a keen eye for detail.
- Utilize effective communication skills to provide customers with information about routes and services, developing strong interpersonal skills.

Compass Group - Chelsea Football Club

Bartender, Team Leader

 ${\it September~2016-September~2018}$

- Lead a team of bartenders, developing strong leadership and management skills.
- Maintain accurate documentation related to work tasks, developing a keen eye for detail.
- Ensure tasks are completed efficiently and to a premium standard, utilizing problem-solving skills to identify and address issues in a timely manner.

Certifications

- Udemy, The Web Developer Bootcamp (64hr)
- Udemy, Dropshipping Empire (12hr)